1. you can trigger both events by a click
2. we have two events 
the first event:
- spawns a beehive aswell as a exit portal within it
- turns the fairies into pollinators and dudes into bees and trees into flowers
- turns all water within a range into a space void
second event: 
- spawns a beehive and a entrance portal
- turns the fairies into pollinators and dudes into bees and trees into flowers
- turns water into void within range
3.the pollinators should replant the flowers(a skin redesign)
4.  the beeworker should collect honey from the flower and drop it off at the houses
the two portals should connect
5. Nick Hotelling: project managing, worked on virtualWorld, and entity behavior
Spruha Nayak: created graphics, imported images, helped design and implement polymorphism
Nick Perlich: worked on entity classes, entity behavior, designing classes
