1. you can trigger both events by a click
2. we have two events 
the first event:
- spawns a beehive aswell as a exit portal within it
- turns the dudes within it to beeworkers
- turns all water into a space void
- trees turn into flowers
second event: 
- spawns a beehive and a entrance portal
- turns the fairies into cyborgs
- also turns trees into flowers
3.the cyborgs should replant the flowers(a skin redesign)
4.  the beeworker should collect honey from the flower and drop it off at the portal
the two portals should connect
5. Nick Hotelling: project managing, worked on virtualWorld, and entity behavior
Spruha Nayak: created graphics, imported images, helped design and implement polymorphism
Nick Perlich: worked on entity classes, entity behavior, designing classes
